<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<news>
    <article>
        <date>May 31, 2015</date>
        <title>Flickr images temporarily disabled</title>
        <body><![CDATA[
        <p>
            Several people have reported problems with repeating images and I
            suspect it has something to do with the way I'm attempting to
            obtain random images from Flickr. I've pulled the Flickr images
            from the pool until I can resolve this. You still have around 650
            "classic" Words That Follow images to play with in the meantime.
        </p>
        ]]>
        </body>
    </article>
    <article>
        <date>March 4, 2015</date>
        <title>Rise from your grave!</title>
        <body><![CDATA[
        <p>
            So, apparently the site had been down since November, and I was
            completely unaware. Perhaps I should be paying a little more
            attention. Nah...
        </p>
        ]]>
        </body>
    </article>
    <article>
        <date>April 2, 2013</date>
        <title>Player list bug fix</title>
        <body><![CDATA[
        <p>
            I have fixed a bug that was showing names in the player list
            incorrectly when they contained certain characters.  I have
            also made a pretty major overhaul of the code that should be
            transparent to you, but if you come across any weird errors that
            weren't there before, please let me know.
        </p>
        ]]>
        </body>
    </article>
    <article>
        <date>January 20, 2013</date>
        <title>Player cap added</title>
        <body><![CDATA[
        <p>
            I have added a player cap of 30 people until I can come up with a way to
			reduce the resource usage that a high number of players has been
			generating.  Hopefully this will prevent the game from being
			disabled in the meantime.
        </p>
        ]]>
        </body>
    </article>
    <article>
        <date>January 20, 2013</date>
        <title>Oops!</title>
        <body><![CDATA[
        <p>
            It looks like my host disabled parts of the site due to high resource
			usage.  Unfortunately, that part of the site is required to play the
			game.  I am working with my web host to get the resolved so I can
			get things up and running again.
        </p>
        ]]>
        </body>
    </article>
    <article>
        <date>March 11, 2012</date>
        <title>Quiet, you!</title>
        <body><![CDATA[
        <p>
            You can now mute people in chat.  To do so, simply click on the player's
            name on the score list.  Their name will turn black and all their chat
            messages will vanish.  Clicking the name again will undo this.
        </p>
        ]]>
        </body>
    </article>
    <article>
        <date>December 31, 2011</date>
        <title>Redirection problem fixed</title>
        <body><![CDATA[
		<p>I found that some devices that do not have Java capabilities were
			getting auto-redirected to Java's website whenever they tried to load the game.  I have made
			a change that should prevent this from happening.
		</p>
		<p>Also, the images to the right should once again display correctly in Internet Explorer</p>
		]]>
        </body>
    </article>
    <article>
        <date>December 21, 2011</date>
        <title>Notification sound added</title>
        <body><![CDATA[
		<p>
			Sound has been added to the game!  Well, just one sound, really.
			A poorly recorded, synthesized chime will now announce the beginning of new rounds.  This
			is disabled by default and can be toggled on and off by clicking the speaker icon in the
			top bar.  To be able to hear the sound, you will need the latest version of the
			<a href="http://java.com">Java plugin</a> installed in your browser.
		</p>
		<p>
			I am honestly not especially happy with the sound I have gone with, but I chose it
			because I couldn't get my Mario Paint composition to record decently (maybe you should
			be thankful for that, actually).  I am open to suggestions for a better sound.
		</p>
		<p>
			In other news, it seems I broke the "Player Caption" image on the right for those of
			you using Internet Explorer.  If you're using IE, you should feel an overwhelming sense
			of shame.  Even so, I will try to find a solution for you poor souls shortly.
		</p>
		]]>
        </body>
    </article>
</news>